<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>A developer's notes in the world of security research and bug bounty, by pmnh</title><link>https://h1pmnh.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on A developer's notes in the world of security research and bug bounty, by pmnh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright © 2022, pmnh; all rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 10:21:50 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://h1pmnh.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Reflecting on 2 Years of Bug Bounty</title><link>https://h1pmnh.github.io/post/2022-sep-2-years-bug-bounty/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 10:21:50 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://h1pmnh.github.io/post/2022-sep-2-years-bug-bounty/</guid><description>
In September 2022, I celebrated 2 years doing bug bounty as the anniversary of my first paid bounty on HackerOne passed. I thought it might be useful to write up some of the lessons learned and some tips and tricks that might help new hunters (things I wish I knew when I started). Bug bounty has been an incredible benefit in my life. It's allowed me the opportunity to achieve a lifestyle of continuous learning as well as transition to a full-time bug bounty career!</description></item><item><title>CTF Writeup: 2022 HTB Cyber Apolcalypse Web Challenge: Genesis Wallet</title><link>https://h1pmnh.github.io/post/ctf-htb-cyber-apolcalypse-web-genesis-wallet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 15:27:19 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://h1pmnh.github.io/post/ctf-htb-cyber-apolcalypse-web-genesis-wallet/</guid><description>
Summary Genesis Wallet was one of the harder web challenges in the 2022 Hack the Box (HTB) CTF. Our team composed of Synack Red Team members finished a respectable 21st place, unfortunately we were very close to solving this challenge and literally were about 5 minutes from a successful solve when time expired - so sad!
Personally I thought this was a very clever challenge and probably one of the best designed web challenges in any CTF I've done to date, so I thought I'd share it with interested readers.</description></item><item><title>LuxCal 5.1.x and below Authentication Bypass: CVE-2021-45914, CVE-2021-45915</title><link>https://h1pmnh.github.io/post/cve-luxcal-2021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 13:23:24 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://h1pmnh.github.io/post/cve-luxcal-2021/</guid><description>
Summary In research related to a Synack Red Team client, I was able to discover several authentication bypass issues in the LuxCal web calendar component. The limited details of these issues, which have been resolved by the vendor in version 5.2.0 of the software, are listed below. As an agreement with the vendor, we are releasing very limited information on this bypass. This resulted in the assignment of 2 CVEs from MITRE.</description></item><item><title>Advanced sqlmap Case Study</title><link>https://h1pmnh.github.io/post/advanced-sqlmap-case-study-1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 23:07:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://h1pmnh.github.io/post/advanced-sqlmap-case-study-1/</guid><description>
Summary Many new bug bounty hunters will blindly rely on the output of tools to magically find them bugs. As most experienced hunters know, the key to long-term success is to understand how to effectively use the many great tools and fine-tune these tools to achieve results in the form of valuable, challenging bugs.
Since I joined the Synack Red Team, I have been digging into sqlmap and the intricacies involved in finding SQL injections &amp;quot;in the wild&amp;quot;.</description></item></channel></rss>